the time has come for us to separate boys from men
and let's go crazy
tamo together
we are with brother valeu
this is episode thirty-one
and good intentions
hell is full
don't get it wrong bro
i have to pass a message
for you who are watching old
if you are going to make a partnership
is protected
is on
the side there will make the stop
the side here has to do too
and then we see exactly what is good for all of us
you take care of your interest
and they of theirs
and get in the middle ground it's good for everyone bro
it doesn't just go in the verbal noise no
oh my man
how are you
thanks bro
can take 1 little
guys let's go I'm here with my lawyer
cleizer
man is that bro
now that the brand is growing
we have an expansion project there
first thing you do is not marketing
is not selling anymore
is to shield yourself
is to talk
is to protect
understand contract
and I came to talk to who knows to be able
make sure things go right later
born brother
pleasure zaster
you here at the office
thank you brother
and this one or all he's going to do
he researches
register before
okay I fall into the world
create this brand
we are going to make a new cnkj
Zé's brownie
it will be used as a manufacturing process
Charlie's
Brown White Label
all verbal for now
to boys it's ten plus ten
paper is another story
store
so guy
returning now to Santos
and we go old
I just don't want to wake up